<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Gita Essense</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">C</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">Gita Essense</string>
    <string name="Bottom_title_on_splash">Çré Çrémad Bhaktivedänta Näräyaëa 
Gosvämé Mahäräja</string>
    <string name="splash_title">The essense of the Bhagavad-Gita</string>
    <string name="splash_top_subtitle">çré çré guru-gauräìgau jayataù</string>
    <string name="contents_ch0">Introduction</string>
    <string name="contents_ch1"> - Always Think of Me...man-manä bhava - </string>
    <string name="contents_ch2"> - Become My Devotee...mad bhakto - </string>
    <string name="contents_ch3"> - Worship Me and Offer Obeisances to Me
...mad yäjé mäà namaskuru - </string>
    <!-- Chapter 01 Text-->
    <string name="chapter_01">


</string>
    <string name="introduction">
TheBhagavad-gétä(The Song of God) was spoken by Çré Kåñëa 
to his disciple and friend Arjuna, over 5,000 years ago, just 
before the beginning of the epic Mahäbhärata War. Since that 
time seekers of sacred wisdom have turned to the Bhagavad-gétä
for answers to the most profound mysteries of life.
The material in this book was taken from lectures on the 
confidential meanings of the Bhagavad-gétä, given by one of 
the most prominent spiritual authorities of the modern era, Çré 
Çrémad Bhaktivedänta Näräyaëa Gosvämé Mahäräja. He is a 
fully realized spiritual master in the Gauòéya Vaiñëava disciplic 
succession, extant since the time of Lord Kåñëa Himself. Çréla 
Bhaktivedänta Näräyaëa Gosvämé Mahäräja has been teaching 
the ancient science of Kåñëa consciousness for over sixty years. 
In these talks, Çréla Näräyaëa Mahäräja reveals truths of the 
Bhagavad-gétäthat have been carefully maintained and handed 
down in an unbroken succession of self-realized spiritual 
teachers for the last 5,000 years. 
The eminent 19th century saint and scholar, Çréla 
Saccidänanda Bhaktivinoda Öhäkura has said in his explanation 
of theGétä, “When the supremely compassionate Lord Çré Kåñëa, 
whose vows are infallible, spoke Çrémad  Bhagavad-gétä, He 
seemed to be directing His words at His friend Arjuna. Actually 
however, He manifested this scripture for the deliverance of 
the whole world. It is the very form of deep reflection on the 
essential meanings of all the Vedas, and it is the sole means of 
attaining the highest goal.”
Citing Çré Kåñëa’s own words in the Bhagavad-gétäto 
establish pure love and devotion to God as the topmost goal 
of all spiritual seekers, Çréla Näräyaëa Mahäräja explains the 
journey of the soul towards that ultimate level of spiritual 
consciousness. Of all the verses in the Bhagavad-gétä, the most 
revealing is in the final chapter where Çré Kåñëa says, “Always 
think of Me, become My devotee, worship Me and offer your 
respects unto Me. Thus you will certainly come to me. I promise 
you this because you are My very dear friend.” (Bhagavad-gétä
18.65) 
In this verse are four distinct instructions, which offer 
devotees of different eligibilities the opportunity to connect 
with the Lord in perfect loving service. Çréla Näräyaëa 
Mahäräja brings this subject to life through enchanting tales 
from the lives of real devotees, some quite famous, and others 
virtually unknown. The common theme is the extraordinary 
connection they experience with the Lord by the bestowal of 
His sweet, unlimited compassion and mercy. 
It is the sincere hope and prayer of the editors that by hearing 
these wonderful deliberations, all may find inspiration and 
guidance in their own sacred calling. On behalf of the many 
devotees serving in Gauòéya Vedänta Publications, we offer 
this publication to Çréla Gurudeva, praying that he be pleased 
with our efforts.
Humbly in the service of Hari, Guru and Vaiñëavas,
Bhaktivedänta Vaikhanas Mahäräja
Çré Rädhäñöamé
8th September, 2008
Bangalore, India

	</string>
    <string name="selectlang_ru">Russian version</string>
    <string name="selectlang_en">English version</string>
</resources>
